<!--
<i2p.news date="$Date: 2013-03-08 00:00:00 $">
<i2p.release version="0.9.5" date="2013/03/08" minVersion="0.6" su2Torrent="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:98b8b69b5aacda5267f4b05236a85248819b2228&dn=i2pupdate-0.9.5.su2&tr=http://tracker2.postman.i2p/announce.php" sudTorrent="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:5cc8a837b2fa9c80429a1672d34280ad17bbd740&dn=i2pupdate-0.9.5.sud&tr=http://tracker2.postman.i2p/announce.php" />
-->
<div lang="en"><h3>2013-04-25: <b><a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/halloffame">Some I2P funding on hold</a></b></h3>
<p>
With the recent rise in value of BTC, the core I2P team decided to exchange some of the I2P general fund BTC reserves
into &euro; to have these safe in our account, as the exchange rate of BTC was too volatile and the price increase
was unlikely to last. We put parts of the I2P general fund BTC into different exchange platforms to ensure we were
not dependent on any one of them, minimizing the risk of loss. It is both fortunate and unlucky that we did this -
one of these platforms was <a href="http://bitcoin-24.com">Bitcoin-24</a>, which has since been frozen. Because of
this, 7899&euro; of the I2P general fund is currently on hold and not reachable. We are now waiting for Bitcoin-24
to release the money, but there is a chance that this money is lost. Echelon will count this as a loss in the
<a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/halloffame">hall of fame</a> until the money does arrive in the I2P account.
</p>
</div>

<div lang="en"><h3>2013-04-20: <b><a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/ticket919">Workaround for Windows-only bug, introduced in 0.9.5</a></b></h3>
<p>A change was introduced during the 0.9.5 cycle to allow configuration files to be edited with the standard
   Windows text editor.  This change had the unfortunate side-effect of causing our eepsite migration code to
   fail to run on Windows systems. Only original installations of 0.9.5 on Windows are affected by this issue.
</p>
<p>Instructions for resolving this issue can be found on <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/ticket919">our website</a>.
</p>
</div>

