<!--
<i2p.news date="$Date: 2012-01-06 00:00:00 $">
<i2p.release version="0.8.13" date="2012/02/27" minVersion="0.6" />
-->
<div lang="en">
<h3>2012-03-24: <b>I2P dev build <a href="http://echelon.i2p/0.8.13/0.8.13-20/i2pupdate.zip">0.8.13-20</a> for public beta test</b></h3>
<p>	
After the big change of router console and migration of jetty 5 to jetty 6 the latest builds has reached a quite stable state again. With this stable state users of I2P could public beta test latest dev build 0.8.13-20 and check if the upgrade does work flawless.<br>
<b>ATTENTION</b>After update, the router will migrate your jetty.xml files to the new Jetty 6 format. The migration sets the port to 7658. If you have more than one Jetty eepsite, OR your eepsite is NOT on port 7658, OR you have made other modifications to jetty.xml (for example changing the listen address from 127.0.0.1 to 0.0.0.0), you MUST edit ALL your jetty.xml files to fix them up after updating, and restart again.<br>
The 0.8.13-20 i2pupdate.zip update file is available from <a href="http://echelon.i2p/0.8.13/0.8.13-20/i2pupdate.zip">echelon.i2p</a> as the debian/ubuntu packages are reachable via ....
</p>	
<h3>2012-03-08: <b>Announcement of a potential security issue</b></h3>
<p>
As has been reported on <a href="http://zzz.i2p/topics/1112">zzz's forum</a>, it is possible to determine the date that I2P 0.8.12 or earlier
was installed by examining an eepsite's <em>Last-Modified</em> header. Version
<a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/release-0.8.13.html">0.8.13</a> resolves this issue for new installations
by setting the eepsite's files' modification date to the year 2006.
Users that initially installed I2P 0.8.12 or earlier can resolve this by <code>touch</code>ing or removing
<code>robots.txt</code>, <code>index.html</code>, <code>favicon.ico</code>, <code>help/*</code>, and <code>help/lib/*</code>.
</p>
<h3>2012-02-27: <b>0.8.13 <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/release-0.8.13.html">Released</a></b></h3>

<p>
The 0.8.13 release contains several bug fixes and a couple of new features.
We are pleased that the last release significantly improved performance,
and the network is running well despite continued rapid growth.
Upgrading is recommended.
</p><p>
This is likely to be the last release before 0.9, in which we will migrate to Jetty 6,
and introduce a simplified router console home page. Monitor the news section of
your the router console in the coming weeks for more information on the next release.
</p><p>
Starting with this release, the router will
check for and install plugin updates shortly upon restarting after a router update.
To prevent this, add the <a href="/configadvanced">advanced configuration</a>
<tt>plugins.autoUpdate=false</tt> before restarting.
There is also a new update-all button on <a href="/configclients#plugin">the client configuration page</a>.
</p><p>
Routers in certain countries will now automatically enable hidden mode for increased protection.
However, hidden mode may have lower performance or reliability, and is still a work in progress.
To disable hidden mode before restarting, add the <a href="/configadvanced">advanced configuration</a>
<tt>router.isHidden=false</tt>.
To disable hidden mode later, select <i>use all auto-detect methods</i> under <i>IP Configuration</i> on the
<a href="/confignet">network configuration page</a>.
For the list of countries see <a href="http://zzz.i2p/topics/969">this thread on zzz.i2p</a>.
The only country on the list that has more than one or two I2P users is China.
</p><p>
After you have upgraded, check out the <a href="/i2ptunnel/wizard">new tunnel creation wizard</a>.
</p><p>
Say hello to the volunteers on the <a href="irc://127.0.0.1:6668/i2p-help">#i2p-help IRC channel</a>.
<a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/getinvolved.html">Get involved</a>,
spread the word,
and <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/donate.html">donate</a>!
If you find a bug, please enter a report on <a href="http://trac.i2p2.i2p/report/1">trac</a>.
To help on translations,
volunteer on <a href="irc://127.0.0.1:6668/i2p">IRC #i2p-dev</a>
or sign up on <a href="https://www.transifex.net/projects/p/I2P/">Transifex</a>.
</p>
</div>
