<!--
<i2p.news date="$Date: 2012-01-06 00:00:00 $">
<i2p.release version="0.8.12" date="2012/01/06" minVersion="0.6" />
-->
<div lang="en">
<h3>2012-02-06: <b>Net Status Update</b></h3>
<p>
Just a quick update on the current network status: On February 5th, a record
number of active routers were seen on I2P.  The graphs on
<a href="http://stats.i2p/cgi-bin/total_routers_week.cgi">stats.i2p</a>
show that the network has grown to over 14,000 active routers. In
addition, statistics generated from I2P-news fetches show that there have been
more than 12,600 unique requests. Even with this record number of routers, the
success rates for tunnel-building have stayed above 50%.  The fixes included in
<a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/release-0.8.12.html">version 0.8.12</a> have
had a tremendous impact on network stability.</p>

<h3>2012-01-24: <b>I2P Bounty Unit Tests</b></h3>
<p>
The I2P project got a nice donation of 1500 &euro; to setup a bounty of unit tests. Also a nice sum of 100 BTC was donated to the I2P bitcoin client bounty.<br>
Get in contact with us if you think you can code one of these projects and claim its bounty (or another one of I2P <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/bounties.html">bounties</a>!
</p>

<h3>2012-01-06: <b>0.8.12 <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/release-0.8.12.html">Released</a></b></h3>

<p>
The 0.8.12 release fixes several serious message corruption bugs.
It also contains a redesign of the router's congestion control, and continued
optimization of CPU and memory usage. We are hopeful that these changes will
improve network performance. Upgrading is recommended.
</p><p>
Say hello to the volunteers on the <a href="irc://127.0.0.1:6668/i2p-help">#i2p-help IRC channel</a>.
<a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/getinvolved.html">Get involved</a>,
spread the word,
and <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/donate.html">donate</a>!
If you find a bug, please enter a report on <a href="http://trac.i2p2.i2p/report/1">trac</a>.
To help on translations,
volunteer on <a href="irc://127.0.0.1:6668/i2p">IRC #i2p-dev</a>
or sign up on <a href="https://www.transifex.net/projects/p/I2P/">Transifex</a>.
</p>
</div>
