<!--
<i2p.news date="$Date: 2013-12-07 00:00:00 $">
<i2p.release version="0.9.9" date="2013/12/07" minVersion="0.6.1.10" minJavaVersion="1.5" su2Torrent="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:1b7c65123b9edb8fce7fda3fd90aa87bf77805ca&dn=i2pupdate-0.9.9.su2&tr=http://tracker2.postman.i2p/announce.php" su3Torrent="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:8dd078d9cc284e899943e9bfaffb046cdbe24a05&dn=i2pupdate-0.9.9.su3&tr=http://tracker2.postman.i2p/announce.php" />
-->
<div lang="en">
	<h3>2014-01-04: <bt>I2P on <a href="http://events.ccc.de/congress/2013/wiki/Main_Page">30C3</a> was a full success!</b></h3>
	

<p>Those who followed our twitter channels and the different IRC channels during the last 6 days does already know:
The table of I2P devs and fellows on the <a href="http://events.ccc.de/congress/2013/wiki/Main_Page">30C3</a> event was a full success! 
Nearly all the time we were asked about I2P, its functions, its benefit and the technical stuff behind. Also lots
of in detail discussions were started and cooperation with other projects were discussed or even started!<br>
The translations of our new webpage <a href="https://geti2p.net">geti2p.net</a> are in need of more love and translators. The majority of users
already knowing and tested I2P were telling us: you need better docs! So, please get on <a href="https://www.transifex.com/projects/p/I2P/">Transifex</a>, register 
and apply for the language you want to translate. We need more help to get a nice webpage for all interested users out there!
</p>
	
<h3>2013-12-27: <b>I2P on <a href="http://events.ccc.de/congress/2013/wiki/Main_Page">30C3</a> - visit us!</b></h3>

<p>
	I2P got a table in first floor on <a href="http://events.ccc.de/congress/2013/wiki/Main_Page">30C3</a>, just get into building and one stairs up on the right side - and you will hit us directly!<br>
	Visit us, get your sweets, get your stickers, ask us. A lot of I2P knowledge is around at the table!<br>
</p>
<h3>2013-12-07: <b>0.9.9 <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/release-0.9.9.html">Released</a></b></h3>

<p>0.9.9 fixes a number of bugs in the netdb, streaming, and i2ptunnel,
and starts work on a year-long plan to increase the strength
of the cryptographic signing algorithms used in the router, and support multiple algorithms
and key lengths simultaneously. Automatic update files will now be signed with 4096-bit keys.
We now support SSL between your router and your servers for security.
See <a href="http://zzz.i2p/topics/1495">http://zzz.i2p/topics/1495</a> for more information.</p>

<p>
Several of us will be at <a href="https://events.ccc.de/congress/2013/wiki/Main_Page">30C3</a> this year.
Look for us under the I2P banner or at the
<a href="https://events.ccc.de/congress/2013/wiki/Assembly:Youbroketheinternet">YBTI Assembly</a>.
Come say hi and ask for stickers!
</p>

</div>
