<!--
<i2p.news date="$Date: 2011-11-08 00:00:00 $">
<i2p.release version="0.8.11" date="2011/11/08" minVersion="0.6" />
-->
<div lang="en">
<h3>2011-12-24: <b>Merry Christmas everyone!</b></h3>
<p> 
The I2P team wishes everyone a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year! May all your dreams come true.
</p>
<h3>2011-12-14: <b>MTN version <a href="http://echelon.i2p/0.8.11/0.8.11-21">0.8.11-21</a> available</b></h3>
<p>
Since the release of <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/release-0.8.11.html">0.8.11</a>, some very important transport bugs have
been fixed, as well as a reduction in CPU usage. These improvements can be seen in the development versions in MTN.
Update files for these builds are available from <a href="http://echelon.i2p">http://echelon.i2p</a>. To ensure that 0.8.12
is a success, please help test by following the link in headline, grabbing the <a href="http://echelon.i2p/0.8.11/0.8.11-21/i2pupdate.zip">i2pupdate.zip</a>
file, copying it into your I2P folder (without expanding it), and clicking restart in your <a href="http://127.0.0.1:7657">
I2P router console</a>. The update will be applied automatically once I2P restarts.</p>
<p>Debian packages of the MTN builds can be found <a href="http://update.killyourtv.i2p/mtn/">here</a>.</p>
<h3>2011-12-02: <b>New IRC2P server irc.echelon.i2p available</b></h3>
<p>
The new server irc.echelon.i2p (or ez2czsvej5p3z5bquue5q3thujcodfze7ptybctqhnqc7hms5uzq.b32.i2p) has been linked
to the IRC2P network and will provide its services to the I2P users. This will provide more capacity and more stability
to the IRC2P network for future user growth.
</p>
<h3>2011-11-30: <b>New link in <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/papers.html">press and paper references</a> of I2P</b></h3>
<p>
A new link was added to list of <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/papers.html">I2P references in press and academic reviews</a>. 
If you think we missed a reference, get into contact with us on IRC or with a bug ticket on our <a href="http://trac.i2p2.i2p/">
bug tracking system</a>.
</p>
<h3>2011-11-16: <b><a href="http://forum.i2p2.de/viewtopic.php?p=37300">Report on network status</a></b></h3>
<p>
Echelon has written a short report on current network status on the <a href="http://forum.i2p/viewtopic.php?p=37300">I2P forum</a>. 
It includes some background information and is open for discussion.
</p>
<h3>2011-11-08: <b>0.8.11 <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/release-0.8.11.html">Released</a></b></h3>

<p>
The unprecedented network growth starting October 5th
has dramatically increased network congestion, especially on evenings (UTC)
and weekends. The last two releases contained a few changes that we hoped
would relieve the pressure, but unfortunately these measures have been only
modest successes. The primary issue is to limit the number of direct router
to-router connections in the network. This isn't a new problem; we've been
working on it for several years, usually with good results. However, the recent
growth pushed us over the edge once again.
</p><p>
Release 0.8.11 includes several more changes to reduce the number of router-to-router
connections and increase connection and tunnel build capacity. The goal, of course,
is to improve tunnel build success rates and general reliability. As always, there's
a few bug fixes and translation updates.
</p><p>
We welcome all our new users. Please be patient as we work to improve network
performance. Debugging congestion problems in a distributed anonymous network
is a continuing challenge. Please help improve the network
by restarting your router once the upgrade is downloaded.

</p><p>
Say hello to the volunteers on the <a href="irc://127.0.0.1:6668/i2p-help">#i2p-help IRC channel</a>.
<a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/getinvolved.html">Get involved</a>,
spread the word,
and <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/donate.html">donate</a>!
If you find a bug, please enter a report on <a href="http://trac.i2p2.i2p/report/1">trac</a>.
To help on translations,
volunteer on <a href="irc://127.0.0.1:6668/i2p">IRC #i2p-dev</a>
or sign up on <a href="https://www.transifex.net/projects/p/I2P/">Transifex</a>.
</p>
</div>
